{
  "mediumlevelquestions": [
    {
      "question": "What is 27 + 36?",
      "answer1": "62",
      "answer2": "63",
      "correct": "63"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 48 + 57?",
      "answer1": "105",
      "answer2": "106",
      "correct": "105"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 89 + 77?",
      "answer1": "165",
      "answer2": "166",
      "correct": "166"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 34 + 19?",
      "answer1": "53",
      "answer2": "54",
      "correct": "53"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 56 + 88?",
      "answer1": "143",
      "answer2": "144",
      "correct": "144"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 78 + 43?",
      "answer1": "120",
      "answer2": "121",
      "correct": "121"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 92 + 67?",
      "answer1": "159",
      "answer2": "160",
      "correct": "159"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 43 + 29?",
      "answer1": "71",
      "answer2": "72",
      "correct": "72"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 61 + 35?",
      "answer1": "95",
      "answer2": "96",
      "correct": "96"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 72 + 18?",
      "answer1": "89",
      "answer2": "90",
      "correct": "90"
    }
  ]
}
